Amen. Amen. Amen. This is Steve Taylor.
This is Last Day's News. I think it's
Last Day's News. Yes, that's what we're
doing today. I got I got so many things
going on. Sometimes it's a Bible study.
Sometimes it's a radio program. But
today we're probably going to do a
little bit of both. And so today is uh
June 25th, 2026.
Uh I'm your host uh Dr. Steve Taylor,
and we're going to be looking at uh more
uh news uh and the world in the news.
But where we go to find that is not uh
the newspaper or your internet feed.
We're going straight to the Bible. And
so, uh, like usual that we're seeing
yesterday's or actually tomorrow's news,
uh, in, uh, in in the prophets and the
scriptures that we read hopefully every
day. So, Colleen, uh, how are you doing
this afternoon?
>> Doing just fine, Steve. Glad to have you
along today.
>> It's glad to be along today. And, um,
it's glad to be Well, we'll just say
it's good to be here. It's very, very
good to be here. And folks, it's good to
have you out here as well. I don't know
where you're at, what you're doing,
whether you're driving or at home. Uh
maybe you're in a hospital bed. I don't
know that maybe you're uh maybe you're
uh not able to get out. But wherever
you're at, praise the Lord that you're
here. And again, we're going to be again
talking about some prophetic things
going on in the news. And you know what
we're doing today, Colleen, is not so
much uh anything new news, but I believe
we got a lot of listeners out there that
that truly
not only believe what the Bible says and
that understand that basically that
we're looking at prophecy happening on a
daily basis through the geopolitical
circumstances and the current events
that are happening, but that they want
to know um the next or one of the next
events on the timeline so that they can,
you know, they can know where we're at
in the in the process. And so, uh, one
of the things we're going to do today is
just take a look at some of the the
scriptures, uh, that show this war in
Iran, this this conflict in the, um,
[clears throat] you know, this
this Gulf of Hormuz, uh, is not
something that has taken God by
surprise, but exa exactly what you would
anticipate to happen. And by doing that,
Colleen, that people will be able to
respond to and ask and uh not answer
questions that uh that they regularly
might have given to them because that
they are the going to be very soon the
resident expert uh for
people to ask, you know, what in the
earth is going on? You know, what what's
happening out there? Do you expect a
peace deal? Do you expect this and that
and the other? Uh so that's why people
watch uh and listen uh to this radio
station. So that's what we're going to
be looking at today. So Colleen, first
of all, we jumped into a lot. I haven't
prayed yet. We're going to pray in just
a second. Before we do that, uh tell me
how you're doing and uh anything that I
should know about uh what WPMH is doing
uh now. Any any kind of big news I
should be aware of?
>> Nothing that I'm aware of. We just keep
doing, you know, radio programming here
at the station. Glad to be a part of it.
Glad to serve the community with
Christian programming and ministry and
be an outreach and a platform for
ministries both local and and national.
So glad to do that.
>> Gotcha. Well, that's pretty much
everything that you guys always do,
right?
>> I would think so. So, we haven't changed
too much. You know, we're steady as she
goes and and radio is still very
applicable. I think a lot of people do
listen like you mentioned. People are,
you know, whether they're at work and
they're listening or they're on their um
on their iPad or their phone or
something like that, they listen that
way or in their car. Certainly, that's
probably the key way that people listen
to us, but a lot of driving around in
this area and a lot of going back and
forth so people are able to tune in and
get the content that they need.
>> Gotcha. Gotcha. Gotcha. Well, that
sounds good. So, uh I'm going to pray.
You're going to give some information
about how people can in fact give the
information before we even pray about
how folks might be able to uh join us
and do [clears throat] comments and
things of that nature as we go through
the process today.
>> Of course. So, of course, we have the
phone line open for you. If you're just
tuning in, it's 757-488-5299.
757-488-5299.
That gets you into the studio with us.
We can put you on with us. If you have a
call, if you have a question or a
comment you'd like to make, we can do
that. And certainly, you can always
reach Steve offline as well. But we'd
love to hear from you during this hour.
We come on every Thursday from 12:30 to
1:30. Every Thursday.
>> And you're correct. They can reach me
and they can reach me at two places.
It's um what is it? www.debtfreeva.com
uh which is our law practice and uh in
fact if people want to go there they can
either leave us a message directly at
www.dfreeva.com
and then I'll respond to it or if they
want to just get directly and again if
you want to set up an appointment for a
uh we do a ton of bankruptcies here.
That's how we pay for this program. Uh
that Alliance Law funds this program as
a community service so that people can
know what's going on in this world and
uh what's going to be happening in a
very short time. So uh again uh just
kind of give them a plug right now.
www.defreeva.com.
Uh set up a free appointment, go over
your finances if you've got issues. uh
everything from um how to restructure
your debt to stop a foreclosure to stop
a repossession to stop a garnishment to
stop credit harassment. Stop stop. You
contact me and then uh we'll set you up
a free appointment. We'll at least give
you the the facts that you need to kind
of make those kind of decisions. Uh and
it'll always be attorney led, attorney
driven. You can do it from your, you
know, from your your phone or you mean
your virtual appointment, whatever we
want to do. Or you can come into our
brick and mortar buildings. We got four
of those across Hampton Roads and uh
we'd love to see you or talk to you
online and again that's just uh uh what
we do here. Uh but you also can go to uh
steve lastdaynews.com
and that uh if you want to send me an
email there you get directly on my feed
and I'd love to hear from you. Let us
know you know the what you think about
the program uh what you'd like to hear
in the future. Um, you know, subscribe
to our newsletter at lastdaysnews.com
and uh I have to apologize to those
folks that we have been so busy lately,
Colleen. It's just uh really really hard
to explain. Uh we're taking cases on uh
Christian rights case with our Christian
rights ministry. Another organization,
another faith-based organization that we
have that we help Christians on a
proponent basis. Uh that uh we uh
there's a a Catholic kid in in uh in
Front Royal. Uh that he apparently he's
going to the wrong school because
they're not going to let him play
football uh in the local high school
because he's going to the Catholic
school. Catholic school doesn't have a
high school. he pays taxes, wants to use
the public facilities, but uh the VHSL
and the uh authorities to be in in in uh
Warren County. I don't think that's an
appropriate thing for him to do. So, it
looks like we may be uh having to uh tee
up something here because, you know,
just because you go, you know, in the in
the opinion or the the thoughts of the u
uh the state of Virginia that you go to
the wrong school, you're not going to
public school, so therefore you don't
get to use the public accommodations. uh
well that's that's not right. And so uh
so anyhow that we're busy on that front.
We're busy trying to keep people's homes
under uh control and not under um uh
problematic situations and that the um
and of course we're doing what we can do
as far as just promoting the gospel uh
at Trinity Christian Church of Suffach.
And um praise the Lord that if you ever
want to go to our Bible studies which
again today's presentation will have a
large some of the folks in our Bible
study may even be online today or may
call in today. You'll hear some very
similar things that we spoke about last
night. Every Wednesday night we have a
Zoom meeting and if you'd like to join,
contact me. We'll send you a Zoom link.
You'll get involved in a about an hour,
hour and a half discussion. Uh but about
a half an hour we just hang out and we
just talk talk about Jesus. Right?
Malachi 3:16 says they that the Lord
listened, watched those folks that
considered u you know his word and and
spoke about him often. And so we want to
be those people. So with all that being
said, uh we're going to jump into
the um the the Bible study, but before
we do that, we're going to have a word
of prayer. Let's pray. Father God, we
come to you in the name of Jesus. And
right now in your son's name, God, we
thank you. We praise you for loving us
so much that you would send your son to
die for us on the cross, God. That
changed everything. And we thank you,
Lord, that that decision was made in
heaven uh before uh the first breath was
ever blown into Adam's uh soul, God. And
so we thank you, Lord, that you have
called us by name, Father, that you've
called us before uh the foundation of
the earth. And then you prepared a plan
for us uh so that we wouldn't perish,
but that we could live with you forever.
We just praise you for that. And Father,
now God, that we're in this situation
where we're in the last uh throws of the
age, God, you've placed us here. And um
the church is still asleep. Your body is
still asleep. They don't realize how
close, how imminent your return is. Not
that you're going to come in tomorrow
because we don't believe uh that, God.
We know that there's going to be some
tribulation. And we know that we're
going to go through uh what you call in
your word uh the absolute worst time
since the beginning of time in the next
few years. And so uh Lord, that's a
sober assessment that you give us and
one that we need to prepare for. We need
to watch for. And Lord, we pray you to
bless those that listen today that they
could see the signs of the times and
then know what to do. So Father, we love
you, praise you, and thank you. And
Lord, that person that needs Jesus
today, I pray Lord you would speak to
them. Let them know that how much you
love them, how much you don't want them
to perish, but that how much you've
prepared a place for them in heaven uh
with you, with your son, with those that
believe in you in Jesus name. Amen.
Amen. Amen. All right. So, let's uh jump
into this
>> again. Yes, you can contact us and um
call in whenever you have a question or
comment. 757-488-5299
757-488-5299
as Steve pulls up his his notes for
today.
>> Yeah, I I was having a difficult time,
but I got my notes again. So, you know
what we're talking about is the quote
unquote Iran big quotes Iran uh US war.
Of course, there is no war. You know,
that uh there was a a war power
resolution I think that the uh house has
passed. Now the Senate has passed saying
don't do any more war. But of course the
official note is there is no war and
hasn't been any since we got out there.
And now there's a peace another big air
quotes sort of uh peace agreement or at
least a memoranduming of understanding
which I'm not sure what that
understanding is exactly but um there's
the reason we're having this is there
was this weapon that nobody saw coming.
And so the question is uh and let's just
begin it this way. Uh, if you wanted to
bring the most powerful nation on earth
to its knees, uh, Colleen, what weapon
would you use?
>> Some kind of nuclear weapon.
>> Exactly. Most people would say a nuclear
missile, nuclear bomb, something like
that. But, you know, the problem with
the nuclear weapon, it only takes out
one city. Iran has found something that
takes out the entire world economy and
it's only 21 miles wide. uh the straight
of Hormuz, a narrow channel that we've
all heard about by now, uh between Iran
and Oman. And in that little gap, 20%,
some people say 20 25% of the entire
world's oil supply moves every single
day. And it's way more than just that
because they got fertilizers, they got a
whole bunch of other stuff that moves
through there that are super important
to feed the world. Uh but you know,
Saudi Arabia, Kuwait, Iraq, UAE, all of
it. uh Iran doesn't need to win a war.
It just needs to keep that window, that
door shut uh of that energy and supplies
that that it is feeding uh so many
folks. And so when the US and Israel
launched the most sophisticated military
campaign,
uh probably very arguably in history,
you know, we had carrier groups, we had
precision munitions, we had bunker
buster bombs, you know, total air
superiority
and the straight did not open. Why?
Because a maritime straight is not an
air superiority problem or issue. You
need to you need what they were saying.
You got to have boots on the ground. Uh
that's the only way it's going to happen
because you know the the way of the
little strike boats and stuff like that.
Apparently we can't stop them even
though we have air super air
superiority. We got all these bunkerb
buster bombs. Uh but the issue was that
Washington, the Trump administration,
probably most folks that would be in
charge of making that decision weren't
willing to put boots on the ground.
Praise the Lord. I didn't want to put
boots on the ground either. And so Iran
has now extracted these frozen funds.
They got a memorandum of understanding
and a ceasefire that doesn't look like a
ceasefire because it seems to not be
ceasefiring a whole lot and walked away
knowing it holds a powerful probably the
most powerful economic lever on the
planet. And so that's where we're at
right now. And people saying, "Why'd you
do this deal? You know, don't do this
deal. Uh you can't trust them." And
they're both right. They they use tea,
you know, the the very, you know, a
doctrine prescribed by their uh
scriptures that say you can lie if if it
benefits you. And let me say another
thing, black mailers, I I can tell you
this because we've seen it in a legal
practice that that is aware of how
things work. Black Mor black mailers do
not cash one check and walk away. They
come back. And guess what happens when
they come back, Colleen?
>> I have no idea.
>> The price goes up every time.
>> Oh, okay.
>> Yep. That's why you don't negotiate with
with black mailers. And here's what no
commentator is saying. This was written
down because they don't know. This was
written down 2500 years ago in the book
of Daniel. So, we're going to be looking
at the book of Daniel today, folks. That
was the kind of the prelim to what we're
going to be looking at yesterday.
tomorrow's news into yesterday's
scriptures that are as live today as
they ever were and we'll tell you what's
going to happen if you just look at it
will help you recognize where we're at
on that timeline. Um and so let's do it.
We're going to be reading Daniel chapter
8. If you're at home, you can read your
scriptures. Uh we're going to just pull
it up. Uh and so let's jump in. So,
chapter 8, most
prophecy teachers, most Bible teachers
will tell you that it's all done. Daniel
8's old news, right? Old news. Uh, and
that the ram was Persia. Excuse me, the
ram was Persia, the goat was Greece, and
that Alexander the Great fulfilled
what was written there in 330 BC.
Nothing to see here. Let's keep moving.
And I understand why they say that. Uh,
and that's what I was taught, at least
for a big part of my my Christian life.
But that's not what the Bible says,
folks. Um, if you haven't read it, then
you should read it. But don't take
somebody's word that basically learned
from somebody else uh, and that hasn't
read or
read it just the things that we're going
to even look at today. So, we're going
to take a look at three verses I'm going
to ask you to read and then you tell me
after you read those three those three
verses. Uh, if you think it was strictly
related to 330 BC or it could have some
application to the end times. Of course,
the end times you'd have to believe that
we're in the end times. And ever since
Israel, folks, we've been in the end
times. I mean, in the very last throws
of the end time. Look at Israel as your
time clock. when she popped back on the
scene in 1948, uh, Jerusalem in ' 67,
uh, uh, we started having that last
generation from 48 until now, uh, the
the the fig tree generation, the 80
years, uh, generation of which things
are getting ready to happen pretty
quickly. So, uh, if this is the end
times, let's figure out if Daniel
applies to it. Uh, Daniel chapter 8, uh,
I want you to read three. We'll start
with verse 17 to start off with and
we'll read verse 19.
>> Verse 17. So he came near where I stood
and when he came I was afraid and fell
upon my face. But he said unto me,
understand, oh son of man, for at the
time of the end shall be the vision.
>> Okay, sounds like the end times. 19.
>> And he said, Behold, I will make thee
know what shall be in the last end of
the indignation. For at the time
appointed, the end shall be.
>> Sound like the end time to me. What
about 26?
>> And verse 26, and the vision of the
evening and the morning which was told
is true. Wherefore shut thou up the
vision, for it shall be for many days.
>> So what what does it sound like the
angel Gabriel um is talking about here?
Something back that happened in 330
years ago or something for the end time?
That's a question to you. Uh that's a
question to the reader to to Colleen.
>> To me. Okay. Well, I mean, I know
scripture, you're always supposed to
take it in the context of when it was
written, but also for for us today. So,
you know, I would say it's certainly
applicable for today.
>> So, when it says that the vision that um
that Daniel saw
and Gabriel says, "Understand, oh son of
man," that's what he's calling Daniel.
"For at the time of the end shall be the
vision." What time do you think the time
of the end is going to what what do you
think the vision is going to be for
which time? 3:30 or the time of the end
>> for now.
>> Yeah. Now at the the time of the end. Uh
what about 19? Uh make these things
known. This is Gabriel saying to Daniel,
he says, "Make the know make you know,
Daniel, uh shall be in the last end of
the indignation. For at that time uh the
appointed for the time appointed the end
shall be." Sound like the end time to
you there?
>> Yes,
>> of course. I mean that the it just says
what it says and it means what it says.
It says that uh three times in chapter 8
uh the father and son and holy spirit
underwriting that statement. Gabriel has
settled the debate. There is an ancient
layer of fulfillment. Yes, Persia and
Greece and Alexander
true story. But the complete fulfillment
Gabriel tells Daniel belongs to our
time. Daniel chapter 8 is an end times
prophet prophecy. And if you believe
that and just got to read it and then
agree with it. You don't have to you you
know you don't have to believe
[clears throat] it. You know, I've heard
people say, "God said it. I believe it.
That settles it." You can just get your
belief thing out of there. God said it,
that settles it. He said it's going to
be You could choose not to believe it if
you don't want to. That's you do that at
your own peril. Uh but it says it's at
the end time and it is at the end time.
And I believe that we are in the end
times. So, um, what does that look like
today? Well, the ram is modern Iran.
Verse 20 is explicit. Can you read verse
20? Calling
>> verse 20. The ram which thou sawest
having two horns are the kings of Media
and Persia.
>> That's the modern succession uh
successor state to uh Media and Persia.
That's Iran. And on the same land with
the same people, it's Iran. It's not
some allegory. That's geography. It's
not allegory. It's geography. That's
what we're talking about. Daniel tells
us in the holy scriptures uh through
Gabriel or actually Gabriel says it
through Daniel uh that we're going to
see Iran in an end time conflict. A
vision that we're going to look at
today. The ram and the goat. He says
this is for the end time and that the
ram is Persia. And then what does the
ram do? Let's read Daniel 8:4. Colleen
>> verse four.
>> Mhm. I saw the ram pushing westward and
northward and southward so that no beast
might stand before him. Neither was
there any that could deliver out of his
hand. But he did according to his will
and became great.
>> Yep. Since 1979, we've seen Iran uh push
to the west Hezbollah in Lebanon, Hamas
in Gaza, north Syria corridor, Iranian
forces propping the Assad. south control
of Iraq, uh the Houthis in Yemen, uh for
30 years, uh the Shia Crescent, that's
that area just above is uh the Shia
Crescent, the the area uh that um that
that borders uh Iran, uh stretched from
Thron to the Mediterranean, and no
regional power stopped it. That's the
ram pushing those directions. Daniel 8:4
fulfilled in your lifetime. You may not
have realized it, but that's exactly
what's been going on. The Bible says it.
It's clear. Now, we have the two horns.
Now, let me just do this because this is
going to be a little bit from the hip.
Uh there's several different
interpretations of the two horns of the
ram. Uh verse three describes a ram with
two horns, both prominent, and then the
second rose later and become greater.
That's what it says. That's it describes
the ram in the latter days. Two power
centers in Iran. And for decades uh that
we've seen the Ayatollahas, you know,
you had uh Ayatollah Kmeni and then you
had Ayatollah Kani and now you have this
guy that we don't ever hear from, but
he's supposed to be the son of the the
Kmeni and he's supposed to be in charge.
And we've seen these these Ayatollah
basically run the religious uh system in
Iran.
there. One of the arguments is is that's
kind of like was the horn that first
came up and now we have the IRGC getting
bigger. And so that's one of the
arguments that we have. We have uh we're
trying to figure out we we don't know
everything about a lot of things, but we
can look and see and say what are the
two horns because we know it's true.
What are the two horns? Some people say
it's the Ayatollas. And then you have
this IRGC kind of the mil, you know,
it's kind of like the military sort of
um
um zealots, I guess, you know, that
hardliners, whatever you want to call
them. Um but they seem to have a very
strong religious affiliation
almost like that they, you know, uh are
really part of those the the same sort
of religious clerical sort of system,
but they're different. So one says,
well, yeah, that with here were the
Ayatollas. Now you have these IRGC
military folks getting bigger and that
the scriptures say that the second one
gets bigger, has more money, gets gets
more powerful than the first. And that's
one of the arguments. Another one which
I subscribe to, uh, Colleen, uh, is that
you certainly have the Ayatollas getting
stronger, bigger, and more powerful.
That's the first horn. That's the
Ayatollas. Um, that's the religious
clerical system. But I see the IRGC as
being as fanatical and as crazy as those
guys were. The same sort of demonic sort
of religion that they subscribe to. And
then so what would be the second horn?
Well, I believe uh that that you're
going to see a very likely possibility.
You're going to see uh Amadi, right? The
uh like the antichrist, you know, the
not necessarily the antichrist, the u
shouldn't say the antichrist. uh you're
going to see their version of their
messiah. That's what I should say. Both
the Sunni and the Shiites have their own
mis Muhammad for the Sunnis and then you
got this um madi. They're both madis. Uh
but that the one's Muhammad, the other
one is in the 12 religion. Uh is this um
this distant uh uh recipient of the uh
the caliphate, the the khalif that's
been in oultation. I mean, he's been
hiding for hundreds and hundreds and
hundreds of years and that he's just
waiting for an Armageddon-like scenario
to come out and then he's going to jump
out and he's going to rescue uh Iran.
And so that that's the one that I
believe is going to come up. Jesus says
there's going to be um you know um false
Christ. Uh I think there's going to be a
false Christ. I think it's going to come
out of the 12 the 12 vers the Shiite
Shiites. And that one's going to get
richer than all the rest. And that's
going to be the second horn. That's the
two horns thing we need to keep an eye
out for. Uh, you know, either the IRGC
getting very very strong, very very
powerful or possibly and more I think
likely you know this this uh this false
Christ this mighty come out. Um, so
that's what that's talking about. We're
just going to be reviewing stuff today
uh Colleen so people can keep their eyes
open. We don't know all the answers but
we do know what the Bible says. And so
when we see these pictures, these u uh
the these word pictures about things
that are going to be happening in the
end times, we need to figure out what
they are and the the the geopolitical
circumstances will tell us that very
thing. Um I don't have any of my callers
calling in. Folks, you call in if you
have questions, if you have thoughts, if
you have a difference of opinion, that's
fine. If you have something you want to
add to, uh please let us know. What is
the number that they can call? calling
>> 757-488-5299
757-4885299
>> and so jump in, let us know what's going
on. What do you think? Uh tell us what
you think. Um we're looking through the
different things trying to get an idea
of what we should be looking for in the
news feeds in in our internet feeds. Uh
third thing,
kingdom against kingdom, nation against
nation.
Jesus points to Daniel 8. Now,
we're going to go back to Matthew 24
just for a verse or two. Uh you know the
verse. Uh you can probably quote it by
heart, but I I want you to read Matthew
24 verse 7 and 8. Colleen.
I caught you off. Thought you were going
to stay in the Old Testament.
>> Do we still have Colleen?
>> Colleen to Earth.
>> Sorry, Steve. I You have a caller on the
line. I was taking the call. That's why.
[laughter]
>> Sorry. Ralph is on the line.
>> Who do we have on the line?
>> Ralph.
>> Yeah. Hey. Hey. How you doing?
>> Hey, I'm doing good, Ralph. How are you
today?
>> Great. Great. A couple weeks ago, you
was talking about the the red horse
rider, the black horse rider.
>> Yeah.
>> And about about the riding in the
streets and all. I think it was the book
of Ezra. You
>> actually second Edris. Yeah. that the uh
uh it's a basically it's a non-cononical
book that was probably written about a
hundred um AD probably about first
century not by it's it's pseudonym
uh as a um written by Ezra like a lot of
the books uh that we see that are books
but yes go ahead and and it basically
fills in uh the um what Luke and and um
and We're talking that very thing right
now. The kingdom against kingdom,
nations against nation. Go ahead. Yeah,
we we were talking about
>> all the Yeah. Hey, uh just first the
most important the reason main reason I
call that program. Is there a way to get
a script that you of that program?
>> Um I don't know if we we have a script
on that one or not, but we might. We
might. I I um I'll have to take a look
if if what what I
>> Yeah, I would love to be I'd love it
because I I would I I wish my brother
could have my youngest brother could
have heard it.
>> Well, we can send you We do post the the
programs afterwards to the you post
those to the website, but I also have a
copy of them as well. So, I would just
need a an an email address or something
like that to or to point you to the to
the link where you can download the
program.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Well, you know, I want to say one
I want to say one thing uh that really
concerns me is we're talking about
nuclear weapons and all this stuff. Uh I
don't hear anything mentioned too much
about chemical weapons.
>> Yeah,
that mean
>> look how many people that it would
damage and kill.
>> You're absolutely right. that horse
and and I think if I'm not mistaken the
last horse rider behold a pale horse
think death and hell follow him wherever
he goes and if you look up that word
pale in I think it's in the Greek uh far
because there's a long time but it has
to do with green gases like chlorine
chlorine and all that stuff
>> it's chloros exactly right I hadn't
thought about that but you're right it's
chloros uh for the pale rider some
people call it the green horse rider uh
but that uh so you think chlorine gas
maybe something has to do with that?
>> Oh yeah.
>> Yeah.
>> I think one of the one of the country
some one of the country leaders use it
against his own people.
>> Uh
>> I heard that a while back, you know.
>> Uhhuh. It wouldn't surprise me. And that
the um I'm sure there's going to be a
lot of things like that that we don't
know exactly what it is, but it's they
they give us breadcrumbs like the one
that you mentioned. you know that that's
a good thing to take a look at. Um
>> well kind of it's kind of the way I kind
of see things is uh like the four
horsemen. Uh the first horse rider goes
out to conquer and conquer. He rides a
white horse has a bow with no arrow.
Well the papacy for years just about
nearly was going to conquer the world
through inquisition through nature's
loyal and then the na and he rides it
instead of god as god infallible. This
is the papacy. All right. The next horse
rider, behold, a red horse has power to
take peace in earth. Well, philosophies,
religions, and all fighting uh and red
is a color of communism as far as I'm
concerned.
>> And he's uh communism, socialism,
Marxism, and it's taking a piece of
really taking a piece from the earth.
The second horse, third horse is a black
horse has scale on one hand and wheat
and b
that's commerce that's uh talking about
commerce capitalism.
And then of course the last horse rider
behold a pale horse. If you look up that
word mark in the Greek, I think it's
chaba, the mark of the beast, which
means which means uh
uh mark
>> like an engraving
>> means
I forget. It's right on my mind. I know
it as good as my own name. Uh the mark
of the beast is uh engraving.
It has to do with
my heavens. But anyway,
>> I think
>> yeah,
>> you know the good thing I'm I'm sorry.
What was your name? Sir, I didn't catch
that. I didn't write that down. What was
your name?
>> Ralph.
>> You know, so the good things that I see
that you're doing, I see that I'm doing
I've seen that other people are doing a
lot of times we don't know the answer,
but we do know that's the timeline,
right? And so that's
>> Oh, absolutely. So, you know that if
you're going to look at a timeline that
you know, we again we may be wrong about
um the exact definition or the act the
actual things that those things
represent. But at least if we're on the
timeline, we can take a look and then
those things will spell them things out.
Whether it's uh you know whether it's
the papacy or whether it's u a m east uh
uh relationship or whether it's uh
chlorine gas or whether it's um you know
some other um great sword that's being
brought like we see in in in the the
second the second seal the um the red
horse you have this mega sword. Some
people think well that's a nuclear
weapon. Other people say no it's not a
nuclear weapon. It's just a lot of
conflict all over the world like mega
conflict. So you know we don't know the
answer but that if we hold on loosely to
our interpretation but then understand
that whatever God says is going to
happen then as at least we'll be you
know I'm saying uh at least we you know
God's not going to reward us for being
right but he is going to reward us for
watching you know if we can if the
doctrine or that the you know the
preciseness of our our guesstimations uh
is less the key I think than being
watchful so that we can see those things
because these these seals um are you
know Daniel says that hide up these
things until the seals are open. I
believe these seals are what he's
talking about. I believe these seals are
this information that uh that the wise
will understand and the wicked will not.
So I think you're doing exactly what we
should be doing, Ralph, and that's
taking a close look, holding on loosely
to the interpretations because we're
going to be wrong a lot. Uh, but that at
least we'll be on the right timeline or
at least in the ballpark. You know what
I'm saying?
>> Yeah. Well, you you you know, as far as
I'm concerned, programs like you got I I
love because you're blowing the trumpet.
That's right.
>> Letting the people hear and understand
what's going on. Have you ever heard of
a scientist by the name of Carl Sanders,
Spokane, Washington?
>> You know, I think I've heard the name.
Tell us more about him.
He's he
basically he's the one that
along with his team created the
microchip that goes in the body through
a a needle
>> hypodermic needle.
>> It's got 250,000 functions. He created
that ship, but it was in the infancy
stage and they needed to be able to put
a battery in it that would charge itself
in the human anatomy in a place that
turns hot and cold in duration of time
to be able to charge it. But he got sick
from cancer, nearly died. And I heard
that Clinton administration came in,
took it over for the for identification
of the nations, and then created a
battery out of some type of new lithium
that would do that. And
>> that word 100 is stigma. I think it says
a sticking, a scratching, or an etching.
And they put that little chip in that
hyperd needle and stick it in your body.
And I believe he said it's the right
hand, but they're doing the left hand,
too. But that's the weaker side of the
man is the left hand. Um, so
they already put it in people.
>> Well, let me do this. Let two quick
questions. What was his name again?
>> Carl Sanders.
>> Dr. Carl Sanders. Yeah. He's got his act
together now. He's going around telling
people about it, warning them about it.
And let me ask you this, uh, Ralph, how
often do you listen to the program? Just
curious.
>> Oh, off and on when I get a chance.
>> Well, that's wonderful. That's that's a
very big encouragement.
>> I guess I guess I've been listening, I
don't know,
two, three years when I get a chance.
>> Well, that's wonderful. And I appreciate
giving us that information. And where
are you calling from, Carl? Ralph?
>> Oh, I'm I'm in Portsworth right now.
>> Portsouth. Wonderful. Well, listen, we
appreciate
>> I live I live in I live in NOFK, you
know.
>> Well, very very much appreciate the um
the the calling in. It helps us uh you
know get encourage us that people are
listening and that they're they're um
you know they're you know that they're
following and that they're um you know
that the uh just you know we're all in
this together and I appreciate you very
much uh Ralph very very much. Please
call in again.
Please call in again and your friends
>> and I'm just look for the website and
hope hopefully like she said, Colleen
said the website might have that
information on it on the June 11th.
>> You you know what you should do is go to
Nelson Walters. Do you ever look at that
program on YouTube?
>> Uh no. Uhuh.
>> It's a playground for people like you
and me. go to go to Nelson Walters uh
and then uh you know type his name into
YouTube. You're going to find his
channel. He has literally hundreds and
hundreds of videos that are you know
they're not all correct but that they're
they're at least searching realistically
and fervently for the answers that you
and I are looking for. Uh
>> Nelson Walters, right? Nelson Walters.
>> Yeah. And if if you just put that if you
just look about uh about a month ago,
two months ago or sometime in the last
month, uh there was a second Edris. Now
I actually I differ a little bit from
his position. His his second Edris take
was that the um the commotions that is
is is found in Luke 21. uh Jesus words
uh that he says Jesus
um took that from second Edris which
would have made second Edris come before
Jesus words and I don't believe that I I
I believe the scholarship is there
that's saying that it's a pseudo nim uh
document uh that basically came up
probably 100 um uh AD having said that
that it's part of the you know that if
you you know so so the answer is is that
there was a uh a lot of writings that
were made that that even though that
Jesus didn't take it from that uh that
it was well known as to what Jesus was
saying and it was then um put in books
like second Ezras uh and that people
understood it as accurate and so uh it
kind of confirms Jesus words more than
uh Jesus confirms that word but still if
you look at that video that you'll get a
lot of good information, some of that
information that we actually used on our
program that day. So, but they got
>> Steve, let me let me leave you this real
quick because I got things that, you
know, that I've heard and I believe um
there's no way in the world that you can
make peace with Islam.
There's no way because they have a thing
a law called law which means it gives a
right of a man to lie to his wife lie to
a man when he's in a fight with him or
you know li in war
>> tequila a good person tequila law and a
good person that I address because she
came to our church was Reetta Gabrielle
she was news anchor woman
and she came to the church and explained
all that and I I met her in the hallway
afterwards and asked her is it true and
she she looked at me and said how did
you know that?
>> Yeah.
>> I told her I couldn't remember. I hear
so much you know read so much.
>> Yeah.
>> But yeah
>> well you know the uh and again that tea
is definitely a u something that they
subscribe by but you know I think it
goes one level deeper than that Ralph.
You got this prince of Persia right? You
got this prince of Greece. You have
these supernatural fallen angels that
have are princes.
>> Oh yeah. Oh yeah.
>> Control those mulas and those folks. And
the reason they're lying and the reason
they got doctrines of of liars is
because you got a prince of Persia that
could care less about the people of
Iran. Uh but that they've got a master
and it and it's not the people of Iran,
it's Satan. And so the these uh minions
of Satan, these these principalities,
uh you're absolutely right. You're not
going to have peace. If people say
peace, peace, there's going to be no
peace because there's an end time. And
it goes deeper. And let me say this to
you. Um and I appreciate you you u
helping me bring this up. Uh I'm writing
a book right now, should be out in the
next two weeks, maybe 30 days at the
latest. And it's called Hidden in Plain
Sight. And it talks about all these
things we're talking about on the
program. And it gives us a timeline from
the beginning of the uh six but the
beginning of the the seals opening all
the way to Jesus return. And um we talk
about you know you have these human
characters but that you know Paul tells
us in Ephesians 6:12 that we don't
wrestle against those folks. We actually
you know the people that are using tea
people that are killing the people of
Iran.
>> Right. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. We know
what's behind We know what's behind it.
That's right. All right, Ralph. Well,
God bless you. Appreciate you calling
in. Please.
>> Well, let me let me tell you let me tell
you one quick story. Okay. Real quick. I
worked in the shipyard. Two men were
getting ready to fight. They were got an
argument. This happened.
And they were just about ready to fist
fight. And there was a deacon standing
there. His he had powerful arms picking
up the skills for years and years. Name
of Deacon Cruz.
And uh the guy reached back. He said,
"I'm gonna knock the hell out of you."
He throwed the punch. Deacon caught his
hand and he said, "Let my hand go,
Deacon." He said, "No, I ain't gonna let
your hand go till you tell me what you
said to that man." He said, "You heard
what I said?" He gonna knock the hell
out. He said, "Son, let me tell you
something. If you knock the hell out of
the man, he going to be a saved man."
>> I guess because the hell's been knocked
out of him. I get it. Yeah, that's good.
>> That's what Jesus come to do. What did
he do? He come to what? Get the hell out
of us.
>> Knock that out. Yeah, that's right.
>> All right, Ralph. Well, God bless you.
>> Anyway, it's nice talking to you, Steve.
>> Nice talking to you, Ralph.
>> All right. Well, God bless you. And
again, folks, uh, call in whenever you
want to that I enjoy the the phone
calls. I' I'd much rather spoke to you
than a lot of things. And so, uh, that
what's that number one more time? Maybe
we get one more before the end of the
program.
>> 757-488-5299.
757-488-5299.
>> Now, this is going to be the quickest uh
explanation of the the rest I got that I
can possibly give you. Uh remember,
we're just trying to identify some of
the stuff that's going on. We recognize
that we've got a a nation called Iran
and a nation we haven't yet identified.
There are clearly end time uh nations or
kingdoms, I should say, because that's
where we're going now. We have this
kingdom against kingdom uh uh uh thing
that Jesus tells us about in Matthew 24.
And it says, "For nation shall rise
against nation and kingdom against
kingdom." And that this kingdom is
basilea. It's a realm. It's dominion.
It's a civilization leading power. It's
not a tribal conflict. That's nation
versus nation. Uh ethnos versus ethnos.
Uh that what uh Ralph was talking about
is the ethnos versus ethnos.
commotion that Luke's talk that Luke in
chapter 1 talks about uh this fighting
between people the civil wars that are
going to happen. That's one thing we're
going to see that uh we saw that in the
um what do you call the um the um when
all back when uh Egypt was going through
that strife a couple years back um
that's the kind of ethnos versus ethnos
that's the kind of conflict civil war
tribal strife. But when you start
talking about kingdom versus kingdom, a
lot of folks, including myself, said,
"Hey, listen. It may have to do, this is
just a couple years ago was my thinking,
may have to do with like the world wars,
you know, the axis powers versus the
allied powers, you know, and it could
be, but very specifically, you always
have to take the hermeneutic that this
relates to the people that it was
originally given to first, and that
those kingdoms would be the kingdoms of
Persia and the the the kingdoms of
Yavon, uh, which would be Turkey and
Iran. And so consider the structure of
Islam. One quarter of the world's
population. That's a big segment. Two
billion people divided into two great
kingdoms. Shia and uh which is Iran uh
about 15% and about Sunnis about 85%. A
sleeping giant that has been fragmented
for a century ever since uh 1921
uh when it was broken apart. And Jesus
tell us that these two kingdoms uh will
collide uh in chapter 8 of the book of
Daniel. And they're going to collide in
the end times. And what we're seeing
right now is not just in Iran, the the
ram, but we're seeing that the goat is
rising, the Sunni coalition in u in
Javon. Daniel 8:5 tells us, "And as I
was considering this vision that was
going on, a heo came from the west, the
face of the whole earth, and touched not
the ground and the goat, and had a
notable horn between his eyes." This is
that kingdom versus kingdom Daniel was
talking about in the end times. Daniel
calls it the kingdom of Yavon, the
ancient nation on the Bosphorus Straits,
geographically modern Turkey. It's an
end time fulfillment that's happening
right now. If you know your geography
and you know your Bible, it says the
goat crossed the earth without touching
the ground. It was full of colar, which
means anger. Um, and what could that be?
I don't know, Colin. I don't know if
it's power uh from the air like that.
It's got this new u um uh fifth
generation fighter that's supposed to be
almost parallel to US fighters of the
same generation. I don't know if it's
going to be drone swarms. You know, we
saw something the other day about these
killer drone swarms that look like
jellyfish. That's that one u that's what
they said that that they they swarmed on
that one uh fighter that, you know,
remember that fighter about a month or
two ago got knocked out. We had to send
a search party and resc him out of the
ocean. They said there was like drones
that attacked, you know, like a secret
weapon. So, we don't know exactly what's
going to happen, but there's going to be
this air power, drone swarms,
overwhelming speed, not touching the
ground. Um, and that some analysts are
um calling uh this this coalition that
Turkey is going to get into with some of
the other um uh Arabic uh nations like a
Islamic NATO. And so this this sleeping
giant, this caliphate, uh, which is what
Ergodan, that's the president of of
Turkey, wants to do, is beginning to
build. He wants to be the khalif. It's
kind of like the pope of the califf, the
the caliphate. He wants to reform this
this this kingdom. So that's the
kingdoms you're looking at. Kingdom
versus kingdom. Look at Matthew 24. Uh,
but then we have to take a look uh at
another thing, the trigger. What
happens? How comes this happens? And
again, we talked about it briefly, but I
think it's going to be what's going to
trigger Turkey to come and attack Iran.
I think it's going to be that Shiite
12ther, right? The 12th IM, the one
that's in a cultation, the one that's
going to come out when everything goes
bad for Iran and rescues him. That's
according to their doctrine. It could be
the IRGC getting stronger, but I don't
think that's going to happen. I don't
think that's what's going to win. And
what happens is after the goat wins,
after the goat defeats the ram in in
Daniel chapter 8, it tells us what
follows. Um, we got four minutes. Go
ahead and read Daniel 88 and we're going
to wrap this up. Read 88 and read 89.
Daniel 88 and 89, Colleen.
>> All right. Daniel 8:8
is
therefore the goat waxed very great and
when he was strong the great horn was
broken and for it came up four notable
ones toward the four winds of heaven and
out of them came forth a little horn
which waxed exceeding great toward the
south and toward the east and toward the
pleasant land.
>> Yep. So what happens at the peak of the
power, the GOAT leader is broken. So
they they come, they knock out Iran,
they get broken up. Don't know exactly
what that looks up, but that's what we
keep our eyes out for. And from this
coalition that gets broken up, the
little horn, the antichrist, emerges
from one of those sub kingdoms. Small at
first, then exceeding great. He doesn't
come out from nowhere. He comes from
this coalition of nations that ends up
attacking Iran. That's going to happen,
folks. He comes from the rubble of the
goats empire. Uh Daniel's chapter 8 is
the prophetic on-ramp to everything. The
seals of revelation, the horsemen, the
great tribulation, the ram and the goat
war is not a sideshow, folks. It's one
of the major wars on the horizon. It's a
door through which the end of the age
walks. So what do we do? Well, folks,
this is what we do. We Luke 21:28 says,
"And when you see these things begin to
come to pass, then look up and lift up
your heads for for your redemption draws
near." Look up, not curl up. Four things
when then we close. First, pray. Pray
that the harvest is greatest in the days
of upheaval. People who have never asked
about God are asking right now. You
know, what's going on with Iran? What's
going on with Turkey? Uh what's going on
with everything? You're the one that
knows because you study the scriptures
and you know the times and what we
should do. That's what the Bible says we
should be at. You know, pray that the
gospel runs ahead of everything that is
coming. The second thing is we proclaim.
You have a framework. It's called the
Bible. It's called the seals. I'm going
to write a book. I've got a book. It's
going to come out. It's called Hidden in
Plain Sight. And that most of your
neighbors do not understand what the
Bible says. don't understand Daniel
chapter 8. They don't understand
prophecy and the sequence that you will
be watching unfold will give you the
answer to the what the people are
asking. Be ready to give an account for
the hope that is in you. Three, endure.
You know, I believe in the pre prank as
you are sure are aware. It tells us the
church is present as we go through this.
You're not going to you're not going to
get the the easy way out. We're going to
go through this. We're going to go
through the birth pains. We're not going
to escape, but we are going to be
commissioned. We're not surprised by the
storm, but we are going to be allied in
it. The third thing is you need to
watch. Watch for Iran's leadership.
Watch for the leader struct the
leadership structure to formally
complete the two horn transition. Don't
know exactly what that is, but watch.
Watch for one man or one situation to
rise over the Sunni coalition. Watch the
straight of Hormus. These are your
signals. When you see them, you will
know where you are on God's timeline and
you won't will not be moved. And then
folks, remember that we're not here by
accident. God placed each one of us on
this earth at this precise hour. He gave
Daniel chapter 8, gave us Daniel chapter
8 so that we would not be caught off
guard. So we would be standing,
watching, praying, and proclaiming right
up to the moment our redeemer appears.
And remember, Jesus says, "When all
these things all these things start
coming to pass, look up because your
redemption draws nigh." Folks, God bless
you. Uh any last thoughts, uh Colleen,
before we close this thing up?
>> No, that's good. It's always good to,
you know, continue to build on the
content that you're doing and keep
people tuning in for for following
weeks.
>> Yep. And so, folks, God bless you.
Again, if you're not saved, get saved.
Give your life to Jesus. Best decision
I've ever made, for sure. Uh, and it's a
gift that keeps on giving, you know,
that praise the Lord. I just before this
this, uh, program, uh, we got this
lawsuit about the, you know, the kid,
the Catholic kid that, uh, went to the
wrong school. That's what I'm going to
call it, the Catholic kid that went to
the wrong school. And just got some
encouraging news, you know, that, um,
looks like that we looks like we might
be moving forward on it. And so, keep us
in prayer out there. Um, lots of work,
lots of lots of uh, lots of opportunity
to do good in the last days. And then
again, keep the book in prayer, the
hidden in plain sight book. I think
that's going to be something that's
going to that hopefully that God can use
to uh to give people timelines and
understanding. And again, we're not
saying that we're all right, but we are
saying that Jesus tells us that we're
supposed to watch. Watch for what? Watch
for the timeline. And guess what?
Jesus wouldn't tell blind people to
watch. He says we have eyes to see. That
means he wants us to know. People say,
"Well, Jesus said in Matthew 24:36 that
no one can knows the day or the hour."
And he was right 2,000 years ago. But he
didn't say that nobody would ever know
nothing. As we get closer, folks, that
like an eye chart, that fuzzy, blurry
letters are going to get closer and
closer. And those fuzzy blurries are
going to become
clear. We're going to know at some
point. That's why he says watch because
you do not know. But if you watch,
you're going to know a lot more than you
know now. So folks, God bless you. Take
care. Uh be safe. Uh get saved. If you
if you aren't saved, get that done
today. Uh but if you're if you're saved,
start living like it. So folks, take
care. God bless. It's always good
talking uh with you and uh you help me
out through these programs, Colin. Thank
you very much.
And take care. God bless. Bye-bye.
America,
we are at war. Globalists and [music]
leftists threaten the highest levels of
our state and federal governments. Our
state [music] houses, Congress, the
Supreme Court, and even the highest
office of the land has come under their
attack. These dissidents [music] are
laboring to indoctrinate our children,
to corrupt our morals, to divide our
people, and are even working to [music]
eradicate God. But the weapon they
cannot withstand, a power that can break
[music] their forces, is a people that
are united under God and armed with his
truth. Now, join Dr. Steve Taylor,
pastor of [music] Trinity Christian
Church of Suffk, director of Christian
Rights Ministries, and president of the
Alliance Legal and the Alliance
Bankruptcy Groups, collectively known as
Alliance Law, for another episode
[music] of Steve Taylor's Last Days
News.